Gabriel Mulero

10313 Stonewind Dr, Fort Worth Texas, 76244* (817) 341-9793 * gabrielalexandermulero@gmail.com

CAREER SUMMARY

Self-motivated learner currently attending Western Governor's University, with 5+ years of windows, cyber security, network experience and knowledge of python and SQL, active Top Secret security clearance. Seeking to leverage a proven knowledge of data communications, end user support, and network build and maintenance skills.

SECURITY CLEARANCE – TOP SECRET

EXPERIENCE

Network Specialist / hardware engineer August 2021 – Current

Teksystems, Fort Worth, TX

- Provide technical guidance for directing and monitoring information systems.
- Design, build and implement network systems.
- Manage the purchase, testing, installation, and support of network communications, including LAN/MAN/WAN systems.
- Provide assistance and oversight support, operating systems operations activites, including computer
 and telecommunications operations, data entry, data control, LAN/MAN/WAN administration and
 operations.
- Create Batch files to automate processes on networked devices
- Perform STIG scans using SCAP
- Use of SCCM to keep software up to date and devices compliant on network.

Service Desk (GOFO Support), March 2021 – August 2021

APEX Systems, Fort Peterson, CO

- Direct line of contact for General Officers including chief of staff for all related executive IT support.
- Manage user accounts, profiles, file sharing, access privileges and overall network and system security for enterprise access management.
- Management of all voice including Cisco VoIP.
- VDI compute creation and management through the use of VMware Horizon.
- Enterprise configuration management including creation and management of user profiles.
- Experience with SCCM to ensure customers receive the most up to date software.
- Serve as a Privileged Trusted Agent and Issue PKI certificates to users.
- Use of SCSM ticketing system to track and troubleshoot systems.

TEKsystems/Jacobs 10th Special Forces Group, Fort Carson, CO

- Managed and provided daily expert assistance to enterprise customers needing IT support Through walk-ins, over the phone or ticketing.
- Installed, configured and maintained over 1000 desktop and laptop PCs and peripherals such as printers.
- Effectively troubleshoot client and server hardware and/or network connectivity issues on a daily basis.
- Removing old equipment and performing data migration to new machines.
- Maintained an inventory of installed software, managing software licensing, and creating policies and procedures for upgrades.
- Work with hardware and software vendors to verify timely product delivery and ensuring that new equipment is installed and ready to operate on schedule.
- Analyzing and making recommendations for hardware and software standardization.
- Closed 90% of trouble tickets on the first call without escalation.
- Performed administrative duties utilizing Windows Active Directory to enable/disable user computers as well as moving them to the correct OU.

Help Desk Technician, Jun 2016 – August 2020

US Army, Fort Hood, TX

- Managed and provided daily expert assistance to over 1200 customers needing IT support within a 9-month time period, through walk-ins, over the phone or through ticketing system.
- Personally, responsible for managing over 750,000 dollars' worth of networking equipment. Including Cisco switches, routers, Taclanes, SKL's, Gator ball, various satellite terminals, and multichannel encrypted radios.
- Collaborated with other members of the IT Team to perform various IT installations and resolve outstanding tickets to increase customer satisfaction.
- Effectively worked with other members of the IT Team to completely improve, redesign and rebuild pre-existing network of over 400 customers within the local domain within three days.
- Utilized Remedy ITSM to actively track and troubleshoot issues within network, while logging all help desk interactions.
- Administered the use of "Windows Active Directory" including account creation, login reset, and deactivation.
- Communicated and collaborated with (RHN) Regional Hub Node to troubleshoot WAN connectivity issues while providing on-site support to resolve Network downtime, which resulted in a 100% network recovery.
- Conducted troubleshooting on a daily basis through phone or walk-ins to resolve problematic trends on customer end user devices and computer systems.
- Oversaw client diagnostics and compiled maintenance records to determine equipment operability and readiness for current and future operation

EDUCATION

WESTERN GOVERNOR'S UNIVERSITY

Bachelor of Science (B.S.) Data Science, expected graduation June 2023)

CERTIFICATIONS

- CompTIA A+
- CompTIA Security +
- CompTIA Network+
- Microsoft Azure Fundamentals
- ITIL v4